JIYEON YOU

zhdzhddlx@gmail.com · Instagram: Iamjiyeon93

Passionate about cosmetics/fashion and digital marketing. Has worked at Innisfree store for 1 year as a sales staff and learned various cosmetic knowledges also maintained 80% of income as before covid in 2020. Easily adapt to any environment through sales staff experience. Get along with anyone well and Good at coping with any arguable situations through teaching experience. Ready to work as a global worker with proper language skills and international experiences.

EXPERIENCE

SEP 2014 - MAR 2015

SALES STAFF, DEAR BABY(AGABANG COMPANY) – CHUNCHEON CITY, SOUTH KORFA

- Provided customer service to 50-100 customers daily
- Managed inventory and logistics adjustments
- Managed regular customers and provided exceptional customer services

MAR 2015 - SEP 2015

CASHIER, BELMONDE MART - CHUNCHEON CITY, SOUTH KOREA

- Provided customer service to 100-200 customers daily
- Managed international customers(interpretation)

MAR 2018 - JULY 2018

STUDENT TEACHER (MANDARIN), KANGWON NATIONAL UNIVERSITY HIGH

SCHOOL - CHUNCHEON CITY, SOUTH KOREA

- Managed teaching documents
- Made PowerPoint documents for teaching
- Provided 2 to 4 hours of teaching for a day
- Managed over 90students
- Got CPR certificate

MAR 2020 - FEB 2021

SALES STAFF, INNISFREE/AMORE PACIFIC – CHUNCHEON CITY, SOUTH KOREA

- Maintained usual income as before covid
- Provided customer service in a fast paced environment to 100-200 customers daily
- Managed regular customers and provided exceptional customer services
- Managed inventory and logistics adjustments
- Managed international customers(interpretation)
- Provided customized service with professional knowledge

EDUCATION

MAR 2014 - AUG 2019

BACHELOR'S DEGREE OF LIBERAL ARTS, KANGWON NATIONAL UNIVERSITY — CHUNCHEON CITY, SOUTH KOREA

- Major: Chinese literature / Minor: Education
- GPA: 4.27/4.5
- Mandarin teacher certificate

MAR 2015 - DEC 2015

LANGUAGE COURSE, BEIHUA UNIVERSITY – JILIN CITY, CHINA

- Major: Chinese language
- Level: Proficiency

MAR 2021 - SEP 2021

LANGUAGE COURSE, KAPLAN INTERNATIONAL LANGUAGE - NEW YORK CENTRAL PARK - NEWYORK, NEWYORK

- Major: English language
- Level: Proficiency

DEC 2021 - MAY 2022

CODING BOOT CAMP, COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - NEWYORK, NEWYORK

SKILLS

- Language: Korean (Native), English (Proficient),
 Social Media: Instagram, LinkedIn Mandarin (Intermediate)
- Platforms: Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint), Photoshop, VS Code, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap